# AUSTIN ROWE Web Developer

(205)-807-4715

amrowe2018@gmail.com

**My Website** 

My GitHub

#### **Skills**

- React
- Redux
- Node/Express
- PostgreSQL
- AWS
- Linux
- Git
- StrongCommunication
- Quick Learner

## Notable Experience Iris Global Harvest

### School of Missions

The Harvest School is a three month school in Pemba,
Mozambique. It includes an optional extended outreach, that I went on, into the Middle East for two weeks. This was an incredible experience that gave me a deep passion for missions and seeing the lost reached.

#### **Projects**

#### RugZilla

E-commerce site created with React, Redux, Node, Express, Paypal, and AWS. You can check it out in production <a href="https://example.com/here.com

#### austinrowe.rocks

My portfolio site created with React. See the GitHub repository here.

#### **Chrome Extension**

Chrome extension created using vanilla JS, DOM manipulation, and OOJ. Can be viewed <a href="https://example.com/here.">here.</a> To view the source, go to the GitHub repository!

#### **Work History**

**United Textiles --** Retail Associate

December 2015 - Present

Whole Foods Market -- Cashier

May 2015 - October 2015

**Zaxby's --** Cook/Cashier August 2014 - May 2015

**Chick-fil-A --** Cashier June 2012 - August 2014

#### **Education**

Team TreeHouse - Front-End Developer Track

January 2018 - March 2018

Node, SQL, & PostgreSQL - Mastering Backend Web Development May 2018

**SQL & PostgreSQL for Beginners** 

**April 2018** 

**Hoover High School** 

**Graduated May 2015**